{
    "subject": "resource/FreeJ",
    "predicate": "ontology/programmingLanguage",
    "object": "resource/C_(programming_language)",
    "human_readable": "The programming language used by FreeJ is C.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9094113707542419,
            "question": "Is C the primary language used in FreeJ development?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.764543354511261,
            "question": "Can you provide examples of how C is used within FreeJ?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7635016441345215,
            "question": "Could FreeJ be implemented using a different programming language?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7319805026054382,
            "question": "What is the role of C in FreeJ's functionality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7267408967018127,
            "question": "Does FreeJ rely solely on C or incorporate other languages?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7148324251174927,
            "question": "What programming language powers FreeJ?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6739026308059692,
            "question": "What are the advantages of using C for FreeJ?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6506996154785156,
            "question": "Are there any performance implications associated with using C in FreeJ?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6211679577827454,
            "question": "Why might the developers have chosen C for FreeJ?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.609292209148407,
            "question": "Are there any limitations of using C in the context of FreeJ?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The programming language used by FreeJ is C.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8580_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Why might the developers have chosen C for FreeJ?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8580_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any performance implications associated with using C in FreeJ?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8580_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the advantages of using C for FreeJ?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8580_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8580_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8580_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8580_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8580_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8580_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8580_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8580_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8580_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8580_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8580_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that \"FreeJ is written in C and C++,\" which supports the statement that the programming language used by FreeJ includes C."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}